Experiment No. 7
Ueno No. 13
Sorry I'm late.
You are indeed late, Tanaka.
I apologize, but I was
on cleaning duty today.
You are indeed late, Tanaka.
Okay, I get it. I'm sorry already.
Love always drives me, and yet
The wind against the glass
creates an image of you
What "color" will that wind be today?
I want to experience it, completely
Off in the corners of the classroom
Through the tiniest of magics
Another miracle occurs!
A premonition of love
My heart shouldn't be so uneasy,
I don't know what's next
Aah! What is it that throws
my heart into turmoil?
This sudden spark
Love always drives me, and yet
Someone, someday, deliver
these feelings to you!
There we go.
So, what will we be doing today?
We shall be doing nothing.
Huh? Oh, really?
I guess I'll work on my homework then...
Tee-hee-hee!
Behold, the face of stupidity!
Tee-hee-HEE-hee-hee! Hee!
He has no idea that right now,
he is addressing an utter FRAUD!
Ueno No. 13 is a fully realized fembot.
The prototype, currently under development,
was customized as an Ueno Model
and installed with a circuit-like thing that
grants it an "otome" style of feminine expression.
As such, it is has proven extremely flexible,
and able to address a range of needs.
Today, I will use the No. 13
to stimulate THAT part of the puberty cycle...
I will leave Tanaka at a loss for words!
Ueno continued in this fashion,
hope within her heart...
that today, Tanaka will take notice
and realize that the "Ueno" at his side is actually a robot
and will seek out the real Ueno.
However! Tanaka...
Say, Ma'am?
You have an eraser I can borrow?
Sure enough, he accepts this Ueno-esque,
artificial life form as the real thing!
No.
Well, fine.
Confirming camera operation!
Yamashita, I'm gonna need some support!
COMMENCE.
Commence. Operation.
OPERATION                                            COMMENCE.
Huh?
Staaaaare...
May I help you?
LET'S GET
AO DAI
It is nothing.
Oh, really?
Staaaaare...
Uh, excuse me.
If there's something on your
mind, please just say it.
You want some gum?
AIR GUM
Gum, all of a sudden?
But, yeah, thank you.
Staaaaare...
Tanaka, I shall rest on your lap.
What's with you today?
Tanaka, I shall rest on your lap. Tanaka,
I shall rest on your lap! Tanaka, I shall rest on your lap!
Okay, understood!
Tanaka, I shall rest on your lap. Tanaka,
I shall rest on your lap! Tanaka, I shall rest on your lap!
Ma'am... What is that thing
you've got on your head?
I do not know.
Well, fine, I guess.
Tanka, you shall stroke me.
Ma'am, has something bad happened to you?
Tanaka, stroke me.
Tanaka, stroke me! Tanaka, stroke me!
All right, all right!
Tanaka, stroke me.
Tanaka, stroke me! Tanaka, stroke me!
Tanaka, stroke me!
That thing on your head is
sort of in the way though.
Better. Thanks.
There. Will this do?
It shall do.
Oh, no! The otome routine it's been
inputted with is going out of control.
At this rate...!
Ma'am, I'd say that's enough, wouldn't you?
DISDAIN
That piece of...!
Ma'am.
I don't know what's happened,
but if something's bothering
you, you can confide in me.
If you can't talk to me about it,
there's always Yamashita-san.
Do you understand?
Tanaka.
Are your feelings for Ueno-?
This is actually the real me!
Tana-
Will you shut up?!
IDIOT!
SCIENCE
Tanaka-
YOU IDIOT!
Stupid idiot!
Tana-
Cretin!
Dotard! Halfwit!
Tana-
Huh...?
LAB
Experiment No. 8
The SummonStat
You know what?
Experiment No. 8
The SummonStat
Some stray dog wandered into class
this afternoon and caused all kinds of panic!
Still, dogs sure are cute, aren't they?
The way they're all fluffy and stuff.
I'm sure we were allowed to
have pets at our place...
The hell, Tanaka? You'd like to have a pet?
Yes.
I am capable of granting such a wish!
Raising a pet brings with
it various challenges.
1) The problem of noise!
2) Health problems such as allergies!
3) Financial burdens and
things of that nature!
The origin of these can be
attributed to one thing!
Do you know what that is, Tanaka?!
No, I don't.
Correct! It is because
it is a living creature!
And that problem can be solved
in one fell swoop by...
this very item!
The SummonStat!
This temporarily divides an
object into the four cosmic elements.
The addition of a plasma-based microstructural
control mechanism during reconstitution
grants it the same level of
autonomous movement AS A LIVING CREATURE!
Put simply, this device can turn
anything at all into a pet!
Woof!
Well, let's start with something suitable...
How about we try it on these tights?
And that's "suitable"?
Making matter ambulatory
requires an external energy supply...
and waste material produced by
the human body is the ideal energy source!
As such, clothes that have already
been worn would seem to be most suitable!
That's not exactly convenient, is it?
Now then! Transform, O
tights, and do my bidding!
Switch on!
Well, it would seem it was a success.
As you were summoned from
tights, I dub thee "Tamon"!
Tamon.
Ta!
It seems he's already taken a liking to you.
What are your impressions, Yamashita?
It feels like a pair of tights.
That's all?
Let me touch it too.
Yes, hello? I'm currently
being sexually harassed.
Yamashita-san, don't be cruel.
Come on, just a little touch.
MANIC GRIN!
The fool! His eyes have deceived him.
Its form may have changed,
but tights are tights!
His affection for Tamon equates
an affection for my tights! Thus...
He is powerless before these
statuesque legs of mine!
He shall submit voluntarily,
bowing his head in submission!
Tamon.
Hey, Tamon! You more or less
get what's going on here, right?
Just stick to the plan.
Hey!
What the hell's your problem?
Maybe it's a kind of homing instinct.
Darn it! This thing totally
won't do what I want!
Tamon.
Just go back to being tights!
Huh?!
So, Tamon will cease to be?!
Hey, let's make sure we're on the same page.
It's not like this "Tamon" thing is alive.
It would just be something that's taken
the form of a living creature returning to normal.
But still....
You two, listen up and listen well:
I'm not looking after this thing.
Tamon.
We did it!
Tamon feeds on waste,
Yamashita, so maybe he can have your sweat or-
Yes, Officer, this is the man.
THE NEXT DAY, AFTER CLASS
Turns out he's really attached to YOU, huh?
This is how it refuels!
Ta...
No matter how big a blockhead
you are, surely you've noticed
I've tried tactic after tactic, right?
You're bound to act this way,
I'm sure of it  the plan is perfect, I think
And yet, why does this exceed my expectations
Feelings I've had come spilling out
Do you love me? (Love me!)
Turn around already
Wait (Wait)
The timing makes me happy but shy
Happy! (Happy!)
It can't be helped, right?
Because (Because)
I want you to pay more attention to me