Experiment No. 17
Jigatights
Ah! My battery's out again.
Yamashita-san, do you
have a cord I can borrow?
Senpai, that's sexual
harassment. I will report you.
I don't think think counts as harassment.
Please don't report me.
Hey, Tanaka! You can charge
your phone with THIS!
That's a big help, thank you.
Where is it?
Here. Right here...
Behold, it is here!
You see this, Yamashita-san?
THAT is sexual harassment.
Love always drives me, and yet
The wind against the glass
creates an image of you
What "color" will that wind be today?
I want to experience it, completely
Off in the corners of the classroom
Through the tiniest of magics
Another miracle occurs!
A premonition of love
My heart shouldn't be so uneasy,
I don't know what's next
Aah! What is it that throws
my heart into turmoil?
This sudden spark
Love always drives me, and yet
Someone, someday, deliver
these feelings to you!
What's this?
It seems wretched bastard that you are,
Tanaka - you were anticipating something.
Unfortunately, what you were
imagining shall not be found here.
Hidden beneath this dress
is today's must-have item...
To wit, THIS!
Hey! At least one of you could look this way!
It's not as if this slightly
mysterious young girl is researching yoga
and just whispering to herself!
Science Club members, line up! Trot this way!
Team, fix your gaze upon my lower body!
At first glance, these may appear
to be perfectly ordinary tights,
but in fact, they are made
of a heretofore unknown material,
a blend of high-density nanowire
and ultra-inductive polymer!
Hey! Let those peepers get an eyeful already!
Yes, I'm paying attention...
Then listen up! In a nutshell,
HEAT GENERATION
EVAPORATION
these tights can take
all the energy we expend
PERSPIRATION
CHAFING
DRYING
ELASTICITY
during our everyday lives
and turn that into ENERGY!
RANGE OF MOTION
Its ability to generate
power is unparalleled,
providing the equivalent of
a full marathon run at 1.21 jigawatts!
It's nothing short of a revolution,
with energy being generated at the crotch level!
It is ultra high-power output
clothing: the Jigatights!
Huh...
Okay, so, please try charging something.
Fine. Watch and learn. First,
I'll take a smartphone cord...
Is this the one?
What are you doing with that?
Very well! We shall begin charging.
Wow, I'm starting to get kind of excited!
...Um, what's the matter?
You have to rub or something
to start the charging process.
Huh? Just move around there where you are.
Why should I have to be
the one to move around?!
It's YOUR cellphone,
so use your own energy to charge it!
There.
Fine, then I'll wear those tights to
generate energy. Please take them off.
I-I swear, you don't think twice
about crossing certain types of lines, do you?!
For you to say that, this
must be part of some scheme,
a plot to take my tights and generate some
SPECIAL sort of energy, right? You pervert!
What's with that face?!
Um, what is this all about?
Enough already! Just hurry up and stroke me!
Yeah, yeah. Please sit over
here to make it easier for me.
Why are you acting like
this is such a chore?!
Okay, here goes.
Oh!
Ma'am, when I rub you, it
really does start recharging!
P-p-pretty great, huh?!
This sure is useful.
You've fallen right into my trap.
Tanaka, you are a child
of the present, prone to
fiddling
with your cellphone when you have free time!
As such, after prolonged use,
your battery is already suffering from wear.
You are required to charge your
phone several times a day.
However! This is a school, and smartphone
usage is prohibited per school regulations.
The places at which you can
recharge it are limited!
But bear ye now witness to
the advent of the Forbidden Charging Spot!
Tanaka will come in search of I, Ueno  the Girl Who Can
Charge on Campus with Impunity  and then
through repetition, will come to associate me
with his craving for all things cellphone related,
such that before long, all his
thoughts shall turn to ME!
Ma'am, this is...
It takes a while to recharge, doesn't it?
Y-you just aren't being forceful enough.
Oh. That makes sense.
H-h-hey, hold on! Wait,
wait, wait, wait, WAIT!
Ooh! Look, Ma'am: It's totally different now.
Go on, look. Take a look down there.
Wow... It's really juicing
up, much more than before.
One last spurt and you'll get your fill!
Where do you get off stroking the thighs
of a VIRGINAL young girl, you sick pervert?!
You're the one that
instigated the stroking...
Dammit!
Ow...
Come on, Ma'am.
Oh.
Looks like it's done charging.
I swear, you get full of
yourself and then just...
Rub, rub, rub, rub, rub.
You STILL want to stroke me?!
Ma'am, please give me my cellphone back.
LAB
Experiment No. 18
SQ-Water
Oh my...
Experiment No. 18
SQ-Water
I forgot to wear THAT underneath.
Sumo a la Word Chain
I've been so busy since noon.
Well, fine. I can put some on pretty quick...
SCIENCE
There we go. First, I've gotta
pull this all the way down...
Hold it right there!
Why the hell are you tryin'
to leave without even saying anything?!
Well, you made it sound like you
were going to change your clothes, so...
So what, Tanaka?
A girl indicates she's going to
disrobe, and you choose to simply leave your seat?!
I guess...
Aaand there you go, second-guessing
your earlier "gentlemanly" behavior.
Just what on Earth is it that you want, hm?!
Even perverts know when to
draw the line, you know!
LAB
There's no way I could change in front of a
horrible man-beast like you! Get the hell out!
The way you criticize people makes NO sense.
Yamashita, spread the purifying salt!
Shake, shake. Shake.
Let me know when you're done changing, okay?
All done!
Maybe, size-wise, it's a LITTLE small...
Are you going to the pool or something?
Oh, my. It would seem the
young man is somewhat mistaken...
This is in fact today's
special item, the SQ-Water!
Space Quantum! Imaginary Underwater Clothing!
It interprets fluctuation rates in
spatial quantum density as waves,
with water molecules expelled from
the device acting as a catch mechanism
that allows one to ride the resulting,
non-existential waves!
Put simply, when this device absorbs water...
Ma'am! You're floating!
Yes. I am indeed floating.
This garment is one giant leap toward
breaking free of our land-based constraints
and embracing the new world of the heavens!
Stroke! Stroke, stroke!
Wow! That looks like a lot of fun.
Chortle! How naive you are!
This half-clothed, aquatic-like state
allows me to be observed in ALL directions,
which no doubt fills you with trepidation!
Let this be burned onto your retinas:
A heavenly angel that can
be seen but cannot be touched...
Like unto a shaft of light, granted to
illuminate the plight of the most pitiable of swine!
So, if you use that, you
can fly in the air, right?
OINK!
LAB
SCIENCE CLUB
M-my apologies for letting
your imagination run wild.
By nature, in order for this device to process
the maximum amount of quantum flow,
its use is relegated to confined
spaces such as these.
Oh, really?
For example, should the door
to this classroom suddenly
be opened, the quantum flow
would go outward and-
Brother! You said you'd lend me
your Thermos after class today!
Ma'am!
Mizuna! Close the door, now!
What about the Thermos?!
Just hurry up and close it!
Sneak, sneak, sneak...
Oh.
Wow, that talk about a shock!
This is what happens, huh?
How long are you...
gonna keep groping young
girls in sexy poses?!
You puckered anus!
Grumble, grumble! I swear...
She asked for help, but THIS is how she acts?
Also, I wonder what Mizuna wanted...
I'd say that calls for a family meeting.