My machine sister has some thorns
kikai no ane ni wa toge ga aru
But she's programmed to have a warm heart
demo demo yawarakai kokoro puroguramu
Have you been eating properly?
gohan wo chanto tabetemasu ka
Make sure you go to school,
gakkou ni mo chanto
and make some friends too!
kayotte tomodachi tsukurimashou
Topology, torus, fractal
topology, torus, fractal
You're daydreaming again, I can see the Z's!
mata sou yatte yumemite guuguu
Null&Peta dove into a sea of geometry
Null&Peta kikagaku no umi ni daibu shite
floating
pukapuka
shaking
yurayura
They're floating around
ukandeiru
Null&Peta were washed over with the waves of math formulae
Null&Peta suushiki no nami ni nagasare
Arriving at a world familiar yet foreign
tadoritsuita no shitteru you de shiranai sekai deshita
Slippery and Sticky!
Big Sister Bikini Battle!
One!
Two!
Thr—
Huh?
World Sister Grand Prix
Null!
Peta?
Fight!
What!?
Hey, Japanese little sister!
Huh? Who are you?
You're gonna fight my big sister!
Wow! She is a real patriot!
Is this professional wrestling?
That's right.
Big sisters from all over the world...
and their little sisters!
Yeah!
Eat my revolution!
Dark baguettes!
So similar!
Clear
Ham...
burger!
A matryoshka doll. Russia!
Dark borscht!
So similar!
Have some dark jiaozi.
Null, watch out!
Is that a horse?
A Trojan horse!
Here comes a new challenger!
From Greece?
Neigh!
Someone's inside!
Identical twins!?
Yeah, they're twins!
Dark—
What's that?
Yogurt, huh? Hello.
My name is Null and Peta.
My name is Gr and Eece, and—
A famous sight!
So it's a cow?
That's interesting.
Bye!
Clear
Peta! Behind you!
From the country of
civil disobedience,
civilly disobedient dark curry!
It tastes awful!
Wait, Peta!
The zero was invented in India.
As scientists, we have to show respect.
And Ramanujan was born in India.
Ramanujan's formula for pi
He was a genius.
Such an original thinker!
A question for you.
With this angle and this load,
what is the moment of force?
Erm, 193.75 kilograms!
Equivalent to—
Equivalent to 387.5 servings of curry!
Blessings on the country of math.
No! No!
Gods of India!
Gods of wrestling!
You won't lay a hand on my sister!
Peta!
I'll protect my little sister!
Come on!
Peta, look out!
No!
Yeah! But what was that?
Wait, my eyes really hurt. No!
You're cheating!
No way!
This is American science!
Yeah!
Woohoo!
Now for the main event!
This is way too slippery!
Dosukoi!
Thanks!
Wow, Peta! You're a Sumo champion!
Weekly Wrestling
It was a dream?
It's time to go home.
We'll have Sumo Stew for dinner.
Peta really is a grand champion!