Experiment No. 21
The Invisi-Bloomer
Hey, Tanaka.
Experiment No. 21
The Invisi-Bloomer
Lie down over there, yeah?
What do you mean by, "There"?
Just, wherever.
What is this all about?
Hm?
Wait, hold on, time out!
Love always drives me, and yet…
The wind against the glass
creates an image of you
What "color" will that wind be today?
I want to experience it, completely
Off in the corners of the classroom
Through the tiniest of magics
Another miracle occurs!
A premonition of love
My heart shouldn't be so uneasy,
I don't know what's next
Aah! What is it that throws
my heart into turmoil?
This sudden spark
Love always drives me, and yet…
Someone, someday, deliver
these feelings to you!
Oh my, Tanaka-kun! How lucky you
are to see the panties of your club captain!
Feel free to thank the gods,
if you like, but unfortunately!
These are, like, totally not panties!
So, why did you try to sit on my face?
Pay attention to what's right
in front of you, you worm!
Yes, it's the Invisi-Bloomer!
These navy-blue "panties" utilize the
air-compression ratio of the surrounding area
Thank you very much.
Please, have a seat.
to create a barometric field
in relation to the sitting posture of the wearer,
making it possible to sit anywhere.
You're not hired.
NOT HIRED
Okay, try this again.
I'll show you how this works using front-row seats!
I'm fine with just general admission.
Okay, here goes!
Well, Tanaka?!
I'm fine for the moment...
You're not just squatting and
pretending to sit, right?
Hey, do NOT underestimate me!
Whoa! Ma'am, you're floating!
I'm not floating: I'm merely
sitting atop the air!
That's sort of mysterious...
I see right through you, worm! You pretend to
not be interested, but you can't hide it, can you?
Here, right before your eyes...
is a utopia with waters you long to drink!
The ribbon-shaped item
on this device is an emergency stop switch
that allows me to use my buttocks freely!
With this, I will use my peach-colored
waters to slake your thirst!
Oh goodness, I'm sorry!
Huh?
Ma'am, are you okay?
It seems the circuits weren't
functioning properly. Let's try this again.
Huh? I think it'd be best to
take a look at it first...
No, it's fine.
Now, are you ready, Tanaka?
Yeah...
Then look, dammit, Tanaka! Look!
Yes, I'm looking.
And so! This is how it works
as I float in the air...
OH GOODNESS, I'M SORRY!
Huh?
Ma'am, are you okay?
It seems the circuits weren't
functioning properly. Let's try this again!
Huh?
I think it'd be best to
take a look at it first...
No, it's PERFECTLY fine!
Now, are you ready, Tanaka?
Yeah...
Then look, dammit, Tanaka! Look!
Yes, I'm looking.
And so! This is how it works
as I float in the air...
Whee!
Watch out!
What the heck?!
I'm not sure what to say to that...
You don't believe in my
device, so you keep moving!
Now you're just being rash...
How to Properly
Dispose of Yetis
Resume your position, Tanaka!
Ma'am, let's just stop this already.
Oh, I'm coming! You ready?!
Look, I'm sitting in the air! Right here!
And, go!
NOW!
Ma'am!
...Yes?
Come on, that's enough.
You're only making your butt hurt, right?
...Yes.
Your device isn't working,
and it's making you angry,
but you're still trying to
fulfill your club duties, right?
But that's no reason to go hurting yourself!
Do you understand?
...Yes.
You're just doing this to yourself!
Okay.
Yes...
I swear....
LAB
SCIENCE CLUB
Experiment No. 22
The Rearscort
I feel like there are
more people than usual...
...Hello.
That sort of reflexive attitude
is common among club members!
And it can be practiced on one's own!
W-well,l that's good to know.
UNREFINED SAKE
AND ME
So, who is that?
That's Minamine, the president
of the Tennis Club.
There seems to be a lot
of tension in the air...
Well, about that!
Our club captian hates guys!
Oh, yeah. Yomogi, I forgot
you were in the tennis club.
That's right!
So, why does she hates guys?
Well, she's hit a rather difficult age...
So, Uen-san, about that
thing I asked you for...
It's done.
The Rear-skirt!
Its sensors can detect particles
unique to the male gaze,
and its cloth-based artificial
musculature will adjust the angle as needed,
thus preventing the exposure
of worn items that are of a sensitive nature.
This is what you asked for, I guess.
Thank you very much! This skirt is...
it's what we girls in the Tennis Club
have dreamed of for years!
The skirt! In terms of elegance
and ease of motion, it's been rightfully called
the one item of clothing that
epitomizes women's tennis.
And yet, this culmination of beauty attracts
a great amount of lewd and unwanted stares!
can make men curious regarding
what lies beneath.
Blah Blah Blah
Blah
However, and this is not limited
to a uniform of this nature,
when wearing a skirt is required, should supplementary
clothing such that the undergarments cannot be seen
(by which is meant, they cannot be "peeped" upon),
should this become a necessity,
such would of course be welcome so
as to prevent the aforementioned peeping,
allowing a range of motion while
avoiding gazes that are not welcome.
Of course, this is not to say that being
looked upon is entirely displeasing, to a certain extent,
but this tends to stray into
the realm of misunderstanding,
not to mention CONSENT, wouldn't you say?
Are you in acknowledgment
of the facts as stated?!
Y-yes! I do believe I'm in acknowledgment...
I have undertaken various
routes to combat this problem!
I held schoolwide lectures...
These are not panties!
Not panties! No!
I broadcast videos on campus...
I even put up signs around the tennis court.
No Panties!!
I'd say that is WHY you've
gotten so much attention...
No Panties
And yet, my efforts bore no fruit!
It did nothing to prevent the waves of lecherous men!
No Panties
We held study sessions in behavioral ecology
before finally arriving at a single conclusion:
The reason skirts attract attention is
the possibility that SOMETHING can be seen!
And so, the skirt I've requested
takes that possibility and-
Minamine-san! If you're going to change,
please do it in the next room!
Huh? I'm fine doing it right here.
Well, I mean, there is a MAN present...
You have a problem or something?!
Huh?!
Um, well, I don't think it would be
proper to talk as if it's a "problem" or anything...
You didn't understand a single thing
I just talked about, did you?
Now listen! This is NOT underwear!!
These garments have been placed at
the in precisely the OPPOSITE location,
so that the actual underwear is not seen!
How can you see these and think them lewd?
What do you, Ueno-san?
This man is the enemy, and they are everywhere!
These things walk around
with no moral compass other than carnal desire!
Any form of clothing that catches
your eye becomes a form of lust for you, doesn't it/!
If this sort of clothing
catches your fancy so much,
why don't you go looking at a
sports catalog or something?!
Um, these are just my thoughts no the matter,
But I think the clothing itself isn't
why the men will come to watch.
It's because, well... The person who's
wearing the clothes is what matters.
What are you going on about?! Speak clearly!
ANGER!
Um, put simply...
I think they're coming to watch
you because you're pretty.
SHOCK!
I understand. Thank you very much, Ueno-san.
I think I made her mad...
I guess I didn't choose the right words.
TANAKA!
Huh?
That's what I can't stand about you!
Was what I said really that bad?
I'm just going to go to sleep...
Class 1-6
Tanaka! Grarr!