LAB
SCIENCE CLUB
Experiment No. 19
Kanchikan
Why does my class's homeroom always so long?
Experiment No. 19
Kanchikan
Sorry I'm late.
Please don't rush onto the train.
My apologies.
Love always drives me, and yet…
The wind against the glass
creates an image of you
What "color" will that wind be today?
I want to experience it, completely
Off in the corners of the classroom
Through the tiniest of magics
Another miracle occurs!
A premonition of love
My heart shouldn't be so uneasy,
I don't know what's next
Aah! What is it that throws
my heart into turmoil?
This sudden spark
Love always drives me, and yet…
Someone, someday, deliver
these feelings to you!
...pe me.
Huh?
I said, "Grope me!"
Is she a pervert or something...?
Ma'am, what are you doing?
Hey! Don't go getting the wrong idea, Tanaka!
LOCAL LINE
This mock-up train requires
no additional fees, nor is it a free trial venue.
SEMI EXPRESS
SPECIAL RAPID SERVICE
RAPID SERVICE
LIMITED EXPRESS
Instead, it is a proof-of-concept for...
a NEW type of molestation alert system!
The Kanchikan.
This ornamental device forms
an ethereal bond with the mysterious spirit Kanchichi.
The Spirit Kanchichi
When notice of lewd behavior is received, a Spirit
Meeting is held and
Spirit Meeting
should judgment be handed down,
Out                        Safe
Safe                                               Safe
Safe                                                                        Out
an alert is sent to the
humans in the vicinity.
ANNIHILATION
Available in four colors!
Now do it, Tanaka! Show me the groping
techniques you've so expertly refined!
Um, I've never done that before...
I don't really understand
what would make a person do it.
Now look here, Tanaka:
I'm not asking you to weigh in on the morality of it!
Just consider that when
complete, this device will be
a savior to all those who
have suffered groping!
I understand. Okay, I'll be the pervert.
Ma'am, that thing's really going off...
Yes, well, this is how it reacts
when in the presence of a groper.
So, is the experiment over?
Hey! It hasn't even started yet!
Just wait here. I'll be back soon.
Ma'am...
Pipe down!
Time out!
WAIT!!
Caw! Caw! Caw-razy!
Ma'am...
Yes?
The plan as it was explained before was...
because the device won't
react to light contact,
that would force a gradual
escalation of conduct,
leading to the possibility
that a line will be crossed.
Restricted
That's how the explanation went, I believe.
Ma'am, are you listening?
Yes, sorry. I'm listening.
You're asking, like, "Why?" and stuff.
Shall we stop it?
Huh?
The device. Shall we turn it off?
I just... I can't seem to cross that line!
Then you'll have to do your best.
Do you understand, Ma'am?
I'd like to confirm one more time...
The plan is that, the more restraint you have,
the more extreme the
behavior will become, yes?
You don't have to tell me that AGAIN!
Day duty
Tanaka. Sorry to keep you waiting...
Do you know what happened?
Ma'am, are you okay? You
seem sort of out of it.
I feel like I'm catching a cold.
I guess the device malfunctioned...
If you feel so bad that it malfunctions,
then it's not much use.
We're not done yet...
Is she all right?
Yes! That's the spirit.
She has the eyes of a rotting fish...
Just keep yourself in check until
you've reached the promised land!
Hurry up and do it, Tanaka.
Yes, yes.
Okay, Ma'am. Here goes.
Limited Express
Commuter Semi Special Express
Ma'am, why don't we stop here for today?
I... I hate them! I hate these
hands that refuse to cooperate!
Ma'am, let's get your body
nice and rested first.
After all, nothing's more
important than your health.
Experiment No. 20
Repara-te
Huh?
Is this a burn mark?
This desk sure is beat up, huh?
That beat-up thing will become...
As good as new!
The Repara-te.
The device scans what it touches and then
uses nano-particles to grind down the surface.
Once the impurities are removed,
the resulting shavings are used on a nano level
to repair and reconstruct.
By restoring the missing particles,
the surface takes on a uniform appearance.
In other words, swipe it like this and...
Whoa! It's bright and sparkly.
This part here looks brand new!
It grinds down the surface AND repairs it at
the same time. That's easy to understand, yes?
However, that is only its
secondary application.
It's primary use is...
to remove unwanted body hair!
A simple stroke of these gloves
will eliminate unwanted hair in an instant!
It simultaneously provides skin care,
leaving it silky smooth!
Whoa...
Well, Tanaka? Curious to
try out a little rubbing?
Yes, definitely!
I wonder if legs would
give the best result...
My, how brazen you are today!
Just what technique will you use with the
aim of making these legs be called "shapely"?
Not YOUR legs! You can get
rid of that shin hair however you like!
Are you after the milky-white
skin of a fair maiden?!
Oh. Is that what you meant?
All right, well... Let's do this.
Huh? Ma'am...
Do you even grow leg hair?
Not good. This man is...
He's the type that thinks
girls don't grow leg hair.
This has gone past the intended purpose,
arriving at an unexpected state where
mysterious and PRIVATE areas are revealed.
At this rate, her spirit is likely to...!
Actually, Tanaka-senpai, girls
generally do grow leg hair.
Huh? Really?!
But girls' legs are always smooth,
so I thought that's just how it was.
Because we trim it.
Huh. I never knew.
So, Yamashita-san, you do it too?
Actually, I'm the type who
doesn't grow much hair.
Huh? Which is it?!
This conversation is already contradictory!
Girls normally DO grow hair.
I'm probably a bit unusual.
Tanaka-senpai, you have two younger sisters,
right? So, you should have a general idea.
Mmm, I never paid much
attention to their leg hair.
I'm going to go ask them about it.
Please ask about that once you're back home.
But you're curious too, right?
If I can't come up with an answer HERE, we'll regret it.
I'll be back soon!
Glance.
Facing Sudden
Out-of-body
Experiences
14 Rules
I asked them about it!
According to them...
Leg hair?! Mine is SUPER fine,
so I don't do anything in particular.
But would you mind not asking
a question like that?!
That sort of thing bugged
me from a young age,
so I borrowed some stuff from Mom
and got them all silky-smooth!
You really have no sense of delicacy, do you?
That's what they said.
They had different opinions...
So, when you talk about "normal,"
is it REALLY normal?
Suddenly, I'm not so confident either.
Still, Ma'am, you grow hair, don't you?
Our club captain
is currently napping and unable to respond.
Right now, those who DON'T
grow seem to be in the majority.
Hmm.
Someone else I might be able to ask is...
SCIENCE
And so,
I was hoping to ask your
opinion, Kitanaga-senpai.
Oh, I get it!
Let's see...
I'd have to conclude that...
when it comes to leg hair, girls...
tend to...
grow it!
Whoa...
Oh, is that so?
Well, of course!
I'm in the Swimming Club,
so I see a lot of female bodies,
and naturally smooth legs are SUPER rare!
This is the exception!
So, I guess I was overthinking things.
I'm glad the mystery's been sorted out!
It's normal for girls to grow hair, huh?
Right?