Null, it's morning.
Time to get up.
You'll be late for school.
My machine sister has some thorns
kikai no ane ni wa toge ga aru
But she's programmed to have a warm heart
demo demo yawarakai kokoro puroguramu
Have you been eating properly?
gohan wo chanto tabetemasu ka
Make sure you go to school,
gakkou ni mo chanto
and make some friends too!
kayotte tomodachi tsukurimashou
Topology, torus, fractal
topology, torus, fractal
You're daydreaming again, I can see the Z's!
mata sou yatte yumemite guuguu
Null&Peta dove into a sea of geometry
Null&Peta kikagaku no umi ni daibu shite
floating
pukapuka
shaking
yurayura
They're floating around
ukandeiru
Null&Peta were washed over with the waves of math formulae
Null&Peta suushiki no nami ni nagasare
Arriving at a world familiar yet foreign
tadoritsuita no shitteru you de shiranai sekai deshita
Looks bad...
That looks bad, too.
One of them has a jet engine installed!
That sounds even worse.
Everything seems bad...
Big Sister, Do I Have to Go to School?
Null.
I'm not going to school.
Let's take a bath, then.
What a pain...
The tub is filled to the brim!
Look at that surface tension!
All those molecules thermodynamically driven to reduce free energy!
Have you stopped peeing in the bath?
I only did that when I was a baby.
Of course I've stopped.
Since it's been a while,
I think I'll join you!
But in terms of efficiency,
a shower would be a lot better...
Hey, it's this thing!
Bubble barrier!
Your scalp doesn't quite seem to be clean yet...
Would you like to try a head spa treatment?
A head spa?
What's that? It sounds like fun!
It should also thoroughly cleanse your pores!
That's... a head loss treatment!
Th–This is gweat!
Does it itch anywhere?
Make sure to wake up
on time every day, okay?
And eat all of your fried rice.
Since you'll be nice and clean when we're done,
you can go to school tomorrow!
I'm not going.
So after that, you do this...
See?
I hate the way they all stare at me when I talk.
They don't even know
how to do prime factorization.
Even though RSA encryption is
a ton of fun, and really useful, too...
Hey, that's mean! Give me my bubble barrier back!
A shampoo hat and a
coffee cup are both a torus,
so there's no topological difference!
Well, if you pinch your nose,
a person can be a torus, too!
So what's interesting about
the Poincaré conjecture
is how it had been proven
in four dimensions and higher,
but it took longer to prove
in three dimensions!
As for why it was harder in three,
it has to do with how we exist
in three dimensions!
There are ways to force it for
four dimensions and higher,
but N=3 involves our reality,
and that means more constraints.
In the end, it took a hundred
years to figure it out.
But you know, we live in
a three dimensional world,
and I think it's interesting how this took
longer to prove for our own world!
If o' belongs to O'
then f   (o') belongs to O...
-1
Let's try and go to school tomorrow, okay?
Goodnight.
I'm feeling a bit out of it.
You spent too long in the bath...