Experiment No. 11
II Umbrella
Wow, it's really coming down...
I didn't even bring an umbrella today.
I swear, Tanaka. You're
still using an umbrella?
The age of humanity clinging
to some mere stick has passed...
Thanks to this item!
What are you going to do?
Just you watch.
A picture is worth a thousand words!
Hey! Don't go looking up my skirt!
Love always drives me, and yet
The wind against the glass
creates an image of you
What "color" will that wind be today?
I want to experience it, completely
Off in the corners of the classroom
Through the tiniest of magics
Another miracle occurs!
A premonition of love
My heart shouldn't be so uneasy,
I don't know what's next
Aah! What is it that throws
my heart into turmoil?
This sudden spark
Love always drives me, and yet
Someone, someday, deliver
these feelings to you!
First, we set up this
device here on your head.
Well, Tanaka? Can you tell what's different?
No, I can't.
Correct! You couldn't know that because
it hasn't been turned on yet. SWITCH ON!
Next, we shall use this...
A mysterious device from
which water shall emerge.
What? Hey!
Huh? I'm not wet.
It's like it's some barrier!
This is no barrier! The device deploys
an anti-gravitational field upward,
Creating a low-level gravitational wall
that deflects whatever it encounters.
Attach this, and you yourself form part of an
"umbrella" and releasing umbrella-like properties.
And so, we have named this device...
The II Umbrella!
So, it IS an umbrella.
TANAKA]
Still, this is great, Ma'am.
It will change the whole history of umbrellas.
Indeed, indeed...
Now, humankind will be
able to combat the rain!
The era that follows I, Ueno,
shall live in prosperity and-
Gah!
Ow. I swear, Ma'm. Why are
you throwing kicks at... me?
Are you all right?
Wh-what do you mean?
You just hurt your butt, didn't you?
No, nothing of the sort!
But look, you're holding it.
Ma'am, we should go to the nurse's office.
I shall not go!
Ma'am!
Ma'am...
It would be pointless for me to go!
MA'AM!
There's something strange
going on with your skirt.
It is not strange...
There's no way that's NOT strange!
Something utterly strange is going on!
Ma'am...
I shall confirm the current state of affairs.
You just stay there and wait, Tanaka!
Ah. Ma'am, it's just tangled
up with your panties.
What is?!
That was a close call, I'd say.
Hey! What's all "tangled up"?
Shut up, Tanaka! Just die already!
You're scaring me...
I will now extract it, Ma'am.
Be gentle.
Yes. I shall be gentle. Here goes. Everything
will be fine. All right, here
I go. Just try to relax...
...Ma'am? Ma'am!
Ma'am!
What, Tanaka?
I didn't bring an umbrella today.
Please let me in there with you.
Well, fine. But this is a special case.
Thank goodness!
Hey!
I mean, I'm sticking out halfway.
Please come a little closer.
Okay, fine. Just move your hand.
I swear.
MATERNAL INSTINCT
in Charge
Experiment No. 12
E-Q Booster
It seems the time has come to settle this.
Awaken...
Class 3-4
E-Q Booster!
The Epsilon-Quick Booster!
It suppresses the so-called,
"fifth force, " protophobic X-Boson,
thus increasing or decreasing
the strength of the wearer.
It also has a lever of
unknown purpose: the NAZO!
So, it makes you stronger, right?
This is nothing so pedestrian!
This device instantaneously measures
the power level of one's opponent
and conveys the corresponding
amount to the wearer!
Currently, even one such as I...
have within me the same
destructive power as YOU!
It's not like I'm that strong or anything...
Listen up, Tanaka:
it's the secondary sex characteristics
that affect our physical performance,
causing a sizable gap between men and women.
These individual differences make it
hard for the average girl to overpower a man.
Now then! What if that gap
in performance were eliminated?
What we shall now undertake
is no mere sumo death match!
This is woman vs. man,
with the pride of each on the line...
Final Sumo Match from Hell!
Do you get it, Tanaka?
There'll be no need for you to hold back!
Understood.
This battle will be a
clash of equal strength!
Ready...
Begin.
The victor will be the one
whose conviction is stronger!
Hey!
Ma'am, I'm going to push
you out of the ring now.
I protest, you blockhead!
in Charge
Behold! This was a battle of equal strength,
yet I was the one who struggled.
"My, that's strange" is what
you should be thinking!
Well, you told me not to
pull any punches, so...
You could try to get a clue
every once in a while!
If you simply LOOK, you'll
see I haven't turned it on!
Sorry.
If the odds are in your favor,
you just go all-out for it, don't you?
Huh?
Never mind, dammit!
It's now or never.
Did you turn it on?
Yes, I did!
Ready... And they're off.
Whoa! This is completely
different from before!
The E-Q Booster indeed
functions as I explained,
but that's only the Booster itself.
E-Q BOOSTER
TANAKA
In fact, the power of the wearer
is also added to the equation.
E-Q BOOSTER
UEONO
TANAKA
Put simply, with only his own strength,
Tanaka is completely outclassed!
The skinny arms of a soft young girl...
you will yield to them, helpless to resist!
What's the matter, Tanaka?
Do you lack the strength of conviction?
Huh?
in Charge
Come now. What's the matter?
Is THIS the best a man can do?
How pitiful you are. Are
you a baby or something?
Hey! Where do you... think you're grabbing?!
For men...
This guy's losing it!
For the pride of men everywhere!
Okay! Fine, I get it!
I cannot lose!
You've already won!
I absolutely must not lose!
There, there.
Snooze...