My machine sister has some thorns
kikai no ane ni wa toge ga aru
But she's programmed to have a warm heart
demo demo yawarakai kokoro puroguramu
Have you been eating properly?
gohan wo chanto tabetemasu ka
Make sure you go to school,
gakkou ni mo chanto
and make some friends too!
kayotte tomodachi tsukurimashou
Topology, torus, fractal
topology, torus, fractal
You're daydreaming again, I can see the Z's!
mata sou yatte yumemite guuguu
Null&Peta dove into a sea of geometry
Null&Peta kikagaku no umi ni daibu shite
floating
pukapuka
shaking
yurayura
They're floating around
ukandeiru
Null&Peta were washed over with the waves of math formulae
Null&Peta suushiki no nami ni nagasare
Arriving at a world familiar yet foreign
tadoritsuita no shitteru you de shiranai sekai deshita
It seems like Peta doesn't know
what those things at school were.
I've decided to call them "bugs."
They could have followed us back from space.
What makes you say that?
Cattle Mutilation
Monthly
Similar cases are documented in here.
Cattle Mutilation
Monthly
Yeah, no. That's not convincing anyone.
My Big Sister's Bugging Out!
Take a look at this.
I found it hanging off my weapon.
It's about to do its thing.
There doesn't seem to be a limit
to how much they can grow.
Furthermore, they eat anything in their path,
and they multiply if they eat enough.
Anything, you say?
Yes! They're gobbling it down!
Oh my, if only your appetite was this healthy...
There's plenty more where that came from.
I don't mind, so you guys go ahead and
chow down until there's nothing left!
I was able to kill them with this at first,
but they multiply too fast,
and I can't keep up anymore.
I believe they've already
moved on to devouring the city,
and most likely, the school...
Which is why I came up with this!
A new weapon!
You just made it bigger!
Hey, Peta!
You'd be better off with one of these!
In the time it takes you to pull the
trigger once, I can nail two of 'em...
Uh, who?
On top of that, my hammer
never runs out of ammunition!
I can fight nonstop!
Out of energy!?
Null, behind you!
I know I said this when we left the house,
but it's too dangerous out here.
You should have stayed at home.
I'm telling you, it's fine!
Let's see, where can I charge this thing?
Dedicated
Null, wait!
Wow, talk about convenient!
Wh–What is that?
Look after the house, okay, Null?
All right, I'm on my way.
Poor girl...
Hit by a truck on her way to school.
She was only a kid.
See, didn't I tell you? It's dangerous out here.
But Peta, you...
You were...
For now, just go on home
and wait for me to return.
But you... you never...
That time...
Back then...
You never came home!
I'm okay.
Stay at home and watch the house, Null.
No... I'm coming with you!
You're one stubborn girl, aren't you?