EXPERIMENT NO. 1
ROCKER-KUN
Lab
ssScience
Club
Sorry I'm late.
You're really late, Tanaka!
We've already gotten things started!
I'm sorry, Ma'am. Homeroom ran late, so...
Hmph! Well, fine.
More importantly, take a look at this.
I've finally finished it!
This is the ultimate in portable filtration.
I call it “Rocker-kun”!
FILTER
An original product, the result of
painstaking research: Rocker-kun!
Using this, one can turn even
the most fetid of waters into an oasis,
like that which bubbles
forth from a natural spring!
Huh...
Well, Tanaka? Pretty awesome, huh?
Now then! I present to you
my own purified urine.
She's showing off her pee!
Put that away, please. It's gross.
Wha?! It's not gross at all!
Rocker-kun has turned even the foul waters
expelled from I, Ueno, head of the Science Club,
into the scented liquids
of a 3rd year middle school student!
You don't have to put
yourself down like that...
And so! You must drink my urine, Tanaka!
Is this girl okay in the head...?
Wait, why would I drink that?
What are you saying?
If you don't, you can't know
the awesome power of Rocker-kun, right?
There must be some other way!
You sure are putting up a fight.
You  just don't want to drink my pee, do you?
That's right.
Listen up, Tanaka: Experiments like these
KAPPA
SIGHTINGS
hinge on time, place, and opportunity!
When Rocker-kun becomes needed,
it's a matter of SURVIVAL!
No matter the situation,
your surefire water source, of the quality you need...
IS RIGHT HERE!
Could you not put that there, please?
Well?! Drink my fluids
so that you may survive!
I'd rather not drink from those waters...
You have no sense of danger, do you?
If this were Hell, you would've died long ago!
I wouldn't be in Hell
unless I was already dead.
You've forced my hand...
Hey, Yamashita!
Start drinking my pee.
I could sue you for sexual harassment, Ma'am.
Now, now. Just try some first.
She doesn't want to!
Fine. I get it, Yamashita.
Normally, that would cost 100 yen!
You okay, Yamashita-san?
That pee had neither taste nor odor...
Yes!
Yamashita's tasted it, so now it's your turn.
If she's already had some,
that should be enough, right?
It's pointless unless you drink it, too!
Why are you making this all about me?
"Why?" You stupid...
What?
You dumb sonofa...
OF COURSE I WANT YOU TO DRINK THIS!
Huh?
But why?
Tanaka!
I swear, you've always been this way!
I still don't get it.
So...You need me to drink your
filtered pee to confirm your experiment, right?
Yamashita-san already did that,
yet you still want me to drink...
Ah! So then...
You're being mean to me?
Just drink it already!
Drink it and be grateful,
Tanaka! This is my pee!
Look, what do you want from me?
I made this pee!
Drink, dammit!
Stop it! C'mon, that's dirty!
It's not dirty! It's been purified!
Still, it's pee. That's pee!
Okay, time out! Seriously, that's
gross. It's really gross!
Stop calling me “gross”, you stupid idiot!
This is a difficult time for me!
This doesn't seem like the behavior
of someone who keeps talking about urine..
Tanaka-senpai, you've gone too far.
I'm sorry, but she's acting
pretty weird today.
She is indeed acting irrationally...
My pee... All my pee! I tried so hard,
and drank 10 liters of water to pump all this out!
But I can understand her thinking.
I drank so much, I got all swollen!
Huh?
The truth is, she wants to
be upfront with her feelings,
but the thought has made her too nervous.
I think that's why she chose
this mistaken route instead.
But it will be all right, Ma'am.
I'm sure Tanaka-senpai will come around.
Yamashita...
Senpai, this is how serious she is.
The rest is up to you. Please decide.
Nope, I'm not drinking that.
Dammit, Tanaka!
This is when you should
have gulped it all down!
What's your problem, Tanaka?!
Huh...?
What is your problem? You just stand like
an idiot when someone says they like you?!
Actually, no one's ever told me that...
You've just been told! In
the present progressive!
Huh? By whom?!
Just die already!
You certainly are cranky today.
If there are no club activities, I'm going home.
Hey! Hold on one second! Tanaka!
That fool simply left!
How can he be so dense?!
He's been that way ever
since he joined the club!
Eat me!
Like that one time...
I Give YOU
I give you.
And that other time!
Then, when I was worried they'd shut down our club
with the seniors moving on
and it just being us two,
he was like, "I'm sure two will be enough."
Tanaka totally didn't think anything of it!
Still...
That's what I like about him!
Ma'am...
Maybe you should just slip it
into his water bottle next time.
No. I'm going to to mix it into his school lunch,
then tell everyone over the intercom.
That's. Just. Cruel.
FILTER
LAB
EXPERIMENT NO. 2
KUMATANDER NO. 2
Be sure to hold it steady, okay?
Hey, are you listening?
You're not peeking up my skirt, right?
Hey, dammit!
You need to go along with the skit, Tanaka!
I'm not really a fan of the theater.
Who do you think I'm doing this for?!
That's enough. Please just
give me the bullet points.
You sure are selfish, Tanaka!
I swear, it would be nothing
but trouble if we lived together.
What do you mean by that?
Just forget it already, you damn fool!
Ahem. In any case...
As we just saw, scoundrels tend to focus
their gaze on the lower half of girls' bodies.
One can infer that the reason
for this lies in these frilly pleats!
It stands to reason that the expectation of
panties being under this thin sheet of
draped cloth fans the flames of carnal lust!
And so...
I present THIS!
Kumatander No. 2!
It is capable of manipulating
the mysterious dark matter of outer space,
allowing it to render a localized
area completely invisible!
Let's do this. Switch ON!
Did it do anything?
There, Tanaka! Take a look!
Yamashita's glasses are
brimming with dark matter!
Maybe they're just sunglasses...
Well? Pretty awesome, huh?
Put simply, with one of these under your skirt...
the panty region, which up
till now has been on full display,
can become like that of a figurine
that has no intention of showing you the goods!
Okay, now for today's main topic!
Kumatander No. 2 can prevent panty shots...
but to what angle will
skirt access be blocked?! Let's test it out!
We'll verify by lifting a skirt in 10-degree
increments up to 120 degrees!
Tanaka, you'll be taking
notes. For real, okay?
Understood.
We'll start from zero degrees.
RRRRUMBLE
Check. Nothing visible.
Wait just a moment.
You need to sneak a peek from down here.
Whaaat?
This will do. I can't see anything.
It won't do at all!
This experiment is to verify
its preventative abilities!
You have to look in there! All up in there!
But no one would try
peering up a skirt from directly below.
Just hurry and get an eyeful already!
You're being oddly stubborn about this...
I have never heard a guy
complain so much about being
voluntarily invited to get
up in a girl's crotch!
Let's see
Well, Tanaka?!
Ah. Yes, no problem. All is hidden.
Very well. So far, so good.
Oh, that's right! There's
something I forgot to mention.
I can't see... Can't see...
I have the utmost confidence in this device:
thus, I can say with certainty
that getting a look up
this skirt is impossible!
However, that makes for a
rather humdrum experiment,
which is why I have given
myself a form of handicap...
and I am wearing nothing underneath!
...What?
Good Lord, are you dead?!
I'm already looking from down here,
so just lift it up to 40 degrees, please.
What kind of attitude is that to have
when asking a girl to lift up her skirt, you bastard?!
HYAAAAA!
Check. No problem at 80 degrees either.
Okay! Then it's time for
the all-important 90-degree angle!
Normally, this angle would put one's panties
on full display.
You know what that means, right?
Well, Tanaka-kun?!
Okay, next in line, please.
You're quite good at playing the fool,
Mr. Tight-Lipped Tanaka...
but I know you are already
approaching the boundaries of reason!
You were a fool to step into
the diabolical darkness of I, Ueno.
Regret it all you want, but it's too late!
Check. Can't see anything.
Be embarrassed already!
A girl just lifted her skirt all the way up
when she's not wearing any panties!
You need to need to have
a suitable reaction, you damn fool!
But, I couldn't see anything...
You should totally be imagining how beneath that
darkness, THAT lies completely exposed!
What do you mean, ”that”?
I mean THAT, of course!
That! The one and only “that”! You know, THAT!
Please be more specific.
C'mon, hurry.
This idiot!
...don't.
Sorry? I can't hear you.
L-like, guys have a thing that girls don't.
Why are you suddenly spouting riddles?
It's not a riddle! It's a fact!
Then please show it to me.
Huh?
Yamashita, help!
I can't get a good look, so
I'm going to switch this off.
What? What?!
YAMASHITA!