One curly lock...
for my sister's beautiful hair.
One tuberose flower...
for her lovely smell.
One stuffed animal for her soft skin.
Okay! Let's throw all this other stuff in, too!
She's ready!
My big sister!
#1
in the universe
Sister Complete!
Huh?
It's, uh...
not what I imagined.
Fluffy wuffy wuffy...
So fluffy wuffy wuffy!
And soft—
I wonder if that's a bug...
Gonna have to check the program...
She's just not coming online.
I guess I failed.
Peta...
Null?
Good morning, Null.
Peta? Peta, is that you?
Do you recognize me?
Yes, of course!
Thank goodness! I finally get to see you again!
Sis!
Null!
Stop!
Wait, wait, wait!
These are those things that
kill you in video games, aren't they?
And a bamboo shoot, for some reason.
Her hands look like they're
from a construction site.
'Kay, that should do it.
Null, have you been eating properly?
I have.
And bathing properly?
And going to school?
I have not.
Let's go together, then!
If I'm with you, you'll be fine! Come on!
I don't remember adding that feature...
So soft!
Hold on tight to your big sister.
I think we might be lost.
12,612 kilometers to school.
That's far!
Please don't worry. We'll make it on time.
It's fine! I'm fine with being late!
I'd rather get there late than not at all!
It's okay! If it's for my
little Null, I will go all out!
See you next time!
My machine sister has some thorns
kikai no ane ni wa toge ga aru
But she's programmed to have a warm heart
demo demo yawarakai kokoro puroguramu
Have you been eating properly?
gohan wo chanto tabetemasu ka
Make sure you go to school,
gakkou ni mo chanto
and make some friends too!
kayotte tomodachi tsukurimashou
Topology, torus, fractal
topology, torus, fractal
You're daydreaming again, I can see the Z's!
mata sou yatte yumemite guuguu
Null&Peta dove into a sea of geometry
Null&Peta kikagaku no umi ni daibu shite
floating
pukapuka
shaking
yurayura
They're floating around
ukandeiru
Null&Peta were washed over with the waves of math formulae
Null&Peta suushiki no nami ni nagasare
Arriving at a world familiar yet foreign
tadoritsuita no shitteru you de shiranai sekai deshita