Experiment No. 9
The P-Specter
Ma'am, is it really all right for
us to be at school after hours?
SCIENCE
Experiment No. 9
The P-Specter
Not to worry. I've already gotten
permission thanks to, you know, THAT.
SCIENCE
Still, what on Earth do you intend to do?
I'm sure even you two know the stories.
Our school bears the stain of...
The Eight Suspicious Rumors!
The legend of the mermaid
believed to appear at the pool each night.
Love always drives me, and yet
The wind against the glass
creates an image of you
What "color" will that wind be today?
I want to experience it, completely
Off in the corners of the classroom
Through the tiniest of magics
Another miracle occurs!
A premonition of love
My heart shouldn't be so uneasy,
I don't know what's next
Aah! What is it that throws
my heart into turmoil?
This sudden spark
Love always drives me, and yet
Someone, someday, deliver
these feelings to you!
The legend of the mermaid who
appears at the pool at night.
The pale shadow that stares from across
the Art Department, in a room forbidden to be opened.
Mysterious puddles of water
that suddenly spring forth on school grounds.
Countless eyeballs that inhabit
the small window in the gymnasium.
The tennis court rebounder
that can tell you your future.
The doppelganger of the lab prep room!
The cursed desk in the music
room that swallows up all.
The groaning sound
in the girls' toilet of the old school building.
Ooooooooo
These are the phenomena
known as Hell's Eight Mysteries...
And I'm gonna shed light on all of them,
using THIS device!
The P-Specter! Its Twilight Sensor
and spectrally attuned mic
can capture the activity
of non-human entities
and display an approximated
representation upon its screen.
With this, I can...
send a lovey-dovey message
to any unknown beings out there!
Okay! I'm gonna go scout the school grounds
and solve me some mysteries!
Ma'am, do you plan on scouting
the whole school tonight?
Pool
I think that's going to take quite a while.
Gym
Parking lot
Indeed. It would take until
dawn to check each location.
Tennis courts
Meal supply center
Sports field
Main entrance
Lab (Science Club)
Courtyard
Therefore! No. 13, activate!
Class 3-4
Along with No. 13, we'll form pairs to share
the load and solve this case more efficiently!
I think you could solve the mystery
of the lab prep room right now, though...
We'll start by having Yamashita
and No. 13 check the gymnasium.
Skid.
We'll start by having Yamashita
and No. 13 check the gymnasium.
Tanaka and I will take on the pool.
Understood.
"Understood," he says!
Little does he know
that this course o' mystery we shall take
has already been set with
an array of boobytraps!
It will be trouble after
trouble! Scream after scream!
And when touched by a young
girl's slender, trembling arm...
will your spirit be able
to keep its wits about it?!
Tee-hee-hee!
will your spirit be able to keep its wits about it?!
Sure enough, it's pitch dark, isn't it?
BOOO!
Ha-haa! You got scared,
you got scared. Scaredy-scared-scared!
Actually, Ma'am, it's
just that you were loud.
Ha-haa! You got scared,
you got scared. Scaredy-scared-scared!
I swear... Candle you handle it, Tanaka?
Like, when it really counts?
Okay!
What do you say we get started?
Excuse me...
Ma'am, excuse me.
What is it, Yamashita?
I'll go look for something to wipe that up!
I-I-I'm sorry, Yamashita. I
guess I was a bit too loud.
No, actually... This started before that.
Oh, yeah?
I get it. I guess you're not
cut out for this kind of stuff, huh?
You should have told me as soon as you thought
you wouldn't be able to do this, Yamashita.
But...
But, you put so much work into this plan.
Yamashita... I'm so sorry.
You were trying not to hurt my feelings.
In any case, we have to
do something about this.
We can use any old rag for the floor,
but we need something to wipe you off.
Where did that fool Tanaka run off to?
Please use this to wipe your body.
No. 13...
Oh. You put two layers on, huh?
Please remove your wet clothing.
...All right.
And what do we do about THAT?
I shall initiate cleaning and
water removal procedures.
That's a caregiver robot for you, all right.
Please be sure not to catch a cold.
Th-thank you.
Yamashita-san!
You took your damn time!
Here. Sorry, it's just my jersey.
Also, you can use these.
FILTER
Tanaka... Your "kindness"
doesn't accomplish much, huh?
Experiment No. 10
PE Reserver
She sure is late...
Yamashita-san, did she tell you anything?
No.
The heck? She's been on the veranda?
Ah! It's some stranger!
Sorry 'bout that. It didn't occur
to me it might be locked!
What were you doing out on the veranda?
My business does not involve the veranda.
Rather, it concerns the Science Club:
specifically, Ueno-san.
Gym
Parking lot
Sports field
Front entrance        Lab (Science Club)
This was the shortest route here
from the athletic grounds!
Main Entrance
Lab (Science Club)
Courtyard
Sorry, so, you're coming in from outside?
That's what I just said, right?
But this is the third floor...
Well, well. It would seem that
introductions are in order!
I'm Nishihara, captain of
the Track and Field Club,
and by training daily and getting
the right amount of rest,
I've gained SUPERIOR athletic
skills that defy reason!
Me, shoot, I could climb three stories
using just my right toboggan here!
Don't you think that's a
strange way to refer to your thighs?
But today, I've come to ask Ueno-chan about these
unparalleled physical abilities of mine...
for these superhuman skills are
accompanied by an equally ferocious metabolism!
Behold!
I've sweated so much that all this
water could be mistaken for incontinence!
At this rate, I could be seen
as a girl who indiscriminately squirts pee of joy!
Okay, I get it.
Ueno-chan! Please do something!
I can hear you from out in the hallway!
Here, put these on!
The PE Reserver.
Its ultra-high density,
four-dimensional cross-stitch pattern resin
derived from agar-agar can absorb liquids,
storing up to five liters while
retaining its surface area.
PE RESERVER
CUT SEAWEED-SAN
With this two-piece set on,
you'll be fine even on the SWEATIEST of days!
Okay, I may as well put it on!
Go change in the other room!
STRIP
Yeah... This sure is comfortable!
And it's soaking the sweat right up!
This is incredible, Ueno-chan!
Oh, we're just getting started.
The PE Server has a release valve
that allows you to expel water.
What's more, because it's been purified,
this water is safe to drink!
Recycling!
Here.
Huh?
Go ahead.
Uh, no thanks. Not that water.
What gives? This is a rare chance
to sup on a young girl's bodily secretions.
Nishihara-san, Tanaka is THAT type.
Oh, sorry. I should've noticed.
Here.
Uh, Nishihara-san...
He really is a blockhead
about this kind of thing.
Hmm...
Hey! Shut up with you "Hmm," you halfwit!
Why'd you look like you were
considering it, you slug?!
Well, the top would be
preferable to the bottom, so-
You don't get to go choosing
your preferred spigot!
What's with you? You get mad at me no matter.
So then, what exactly should I do?
You should just be honest.
If you want some of Nishihara's fresh brewed,
first press brew, go ahead and drink up.
Come on, come on...
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on!
So, YOU'RE going to drink it?
ysh, I shll drnk...
What you're saying is unintelligible.
B-DMP
What... What is this feeling?
When I look at Ueno-chan,
sucking so hard like that,
there's this deep throbbing
that rises up from within me.
B-DMP
I don't understand it, but
somehow, my instincts know.
This feeling is...
Maternal instinct.
MATERNAL INSTINCT.
Ooh, there there. You're thirsty, aren't you?
Go on and drink some more,
Ueno-tan. Have more of mama's br-
No matter how big a blockhead
you are, surely you've noticed
I've tried tactic after tactic, right?
You're bound to act this way,
I'm sure of it  the plan is perfect, I think
And yet, why does this exceed my expectations
Feelings I've had come spilling out
Do you love me? (Love me!)
Turn around already
Wait (Wait)
The timing makes me happy but shy
Happy! (Happy!)
It can't be helped, right?
Because (Because)
I want you to pay more attention to me