It looks like I was
out for quite a while.
I even grew a little taller during that time.
My sister...
After the accident,
they said there was almost no
chance of me regaining consciousness.
But she never gave up on me,
convinced that I'd eventually wake up,
and stayed by my side the entire time.
Oh, wow!
Go ahead, take a seat.
Peta?!
Wait... Wh–What the...
She's tiny!
Welcome back, Null!
Welcome back, Null! Welcome back, Null!
Wow, they all look the same!
It's like a party of Petas!
Nutritionally, fried rice is the perfect
dish... Perfect dish... Perfect dish...
You don't have to be exactly like her, you know.
What is all this?!
It's a place I designed so that a certain
someone I care about would never be alone.
My sister created a virtual environment,
where we could communicate
while I was unconscious,
as a sort of rehab for the mind.
The idea was, if I ever did come out of my coma,
I wouldn't feel lost in the real world,
like Urashima Taro does in the fable.
She built it to make sure
I wouldn't get left behind.
Though, if you ask me,
she could've left out the school...
Oh, come on, Sis!
Don't bring that stuff up!
I worked hard on it, y'know?
Jeez...
A Few Days Later.
It's true that I used to be a shut-in
who didn't really take good care of herself,
and who never really saw the point in going to school.
Well, nothing's changed there.
But, because of the time
I spent in the virtual world,
I can now do some of the things
I was never able to do.
Null.
What's up, Sis?
You should have some breakfast,
it's the most important meal of the day!
Here. Eat up.
Th–That's okay...
I already had some of this.
Okay, say "aaaaah!"
Come on, enough with the jokes...
Say "aaaaah!"
Oh yeah, that's right.
If virtual Peta was my big sister,
it makes sense that my
real sister would act just like her.
Granted, her stubbornness
when she puts her mind to something
There you go! I'm so proud of you!
is ultimately what saved me, but even so...
Look after Null, okay?
Understood!
I'll be fine! I can get to school on my own—
Have a safe trip, Null!
Good...
Good morning.
Year 5        Class 3
All right, settle down.
Okay, go ahead and introduce yourself.
An i-intro... i-intro... i–i–introduction...
Null
Uh... g-g-gotta... gotta s-say hi...
On this happiest of days...
On this happiest of days!
It is wonderful to see the families of the bride,
the groom, and other esteemed guests...
I–I–It is wonderful to see the
families of the bride, the groom—
Wait, why would I say that?!
Null
Uh, h-hi, n-nice to meet you...
My name i-is Null...
I, um... I haven't been able
to come to school before now, so...
So cute!
'Round and 'round and 'round it goes!
What is that thing?! A toy?
Wow, cool!
Th-This is my sister, Peta...
Hey now, back to your seats.
Come on, kids.
Everyone, please take good care of Null.
What does it run on? Batteries?
Well, you see...
What's its name?
Null-chan and Peta-chan?
Well...
Nah... Let me think... Hey, I know...
You can just call the two of us:
Null and Peta!
My machine sister has some thorns
kikai no ane ni wa toge ga aru
But she's programmed to have a warm heart
demo demo yawarakai kokoro puroguramu
Have you been eating properly?
gohan wo chanto tabetemasu ka
Make sure you go to school,
gakkou ni mo chanto
and make some friends too!
kayotte tomodachi tsukurimashou
Topology, torus, fractal
topology, torus, fractal
You're daydreaming again, I can see the Z's!
mata sou yatte yumemite guuguu
Null&Peta dove into a sea of geometry
Null&Peta kikagaku no umi ni daibu shite
floating
pukapuka
shaking
yurayura
They're floating around
ukandeiru
Null&Peta were washed over with the waves of math formulae
Null&Peta suushiki no nami ni nagasare
Arriving at a world familiar yet foreign
tadoritsuita no shitteru you de shiranai sekai deshita