My machine sister has some thorns
kikai no ane ni wa toge ga aru
But she's programmed to have a warm heart
demo demo yawarakai kokoro puroguramu
Have you been eating properly?
gohan wo chanto tabetemasu ka
Make sure you go to school,
gakkou ni mo chanto
and make some friends too!
kayotte tomodachi tsukurimashou
Topology, torus, fractal
topology, torus, fractal
You're daydreaming again, I can see the Z's!
mata sou yatte yumemite guuguu
Null&Peta dove into a sea of geometry
Null&Peta kikagaku no umi ni daibu shite
floating
pukapuka
shaking
yurayura
They're floating around
ukandeiru
Null&Peta were washed over with the waves of math formulae
Null&Peta suushiki no nami ni nagasare
Arriving at a world familiar yet foreign
tadoritsuita no shitteru you de shiranai sekai deshita
In this world, no matter what I do...
it looks like I can't die.
Big Sister,
Big Sister!
I'm not sure how much
of this world is actually real.
Even my sister, Peta, whose existence
was the one thing I was sure about...
Even she is gone now.
Maybe doing the things she
told me to do will bring her back?
Is that it?
Will she come back if I go to school?
Easy now...
Well, I considered it.
I'm calling this the
"Oops! I Went to School" incident.
Poor girl...
Hit by a truck on a crosswalk, apparently.
She was only a kid.
Seems she was chasing after
her sister, who'd left before her.
That's right...
It wasn't Peta who got run over that day...
It was me.
An empty world.
You have a lot of time to think
when you're all alone,
and my recurring nightmares
made me realize something.
That day, I was staying home from school again.
I thought Peta had forgotten
some things that she needed,
so I ran after her with them.
And then...
"Does this mean I'm actually dead?"
So I've been trying to confirm that.
A world where I can't die.
Maybe this place is actually heaven.
Which would make this
"Oops! I Went to Heaven" instead.
I'm home.
Every time I come back home,
I remember her words.
Look after the house, okay, Null?
You have to be a good girl
even when I'm not here, okay?
What does that even mean?
Is a "good girl" a girl who isn't selfish?
A girl who always has a smile on her face?
A girl who takes a bath every night?
A girl who gets up on time?
Even when I do everything she said,
it still doesn't bring Peta back.
All right, I'm going now.
Dear Null,
There's some fried rice in the refrigerator.
If you get hungry, microwave it,
and enjoy!
Peta
Disgusting!
Disgusting!!
This is the end.
This might actually kill me.
Took you long enough!
That rice was terrible!
So disgusting that I almost died,
which isn't supposed to be possible!
I don't know what's happening anymore!
Where did you go!?
I go to school now, you know!
I clean the house, I fold the laundry,
I even get up early!
Even though I break my alarm clock
all the time by overwinding it!
And... I won't be selfish anymore,
so come back home, okay?
I'll even take more steps
into school tomorrow if you do.
I'll make friends... and I'll stop
being such a picky eater... so...
Stay with me, please!
Please... Please, Peta!
Sis?