My machine sister has some thorns
kikai no ane ni wa toge ga aru
But she's programmed to have a warm heart
demo demo yawarakai kokoro puroguramu
Have you been eating properly?
gohan wo chanto tabetemasu ka
Make sure you go to school,
gakkou ni mo chanto
and make some friends too!
kayotte tomodachi tsukurimashou
Topology, torus, fractal
topology, torus, fractal
You're daydreaming again, I can see the Z's!
mata sou yatte yumemite guuguu
Null&Peta dove into a sea of geometry
Null&Peta kikagaku no umi ni daibu shite
floating
pukapuka
shaking
yurayura
They're floating around
ukandeiru
Null&Peta were washed over with the waves of math formulae
Null&Peta suushiki no nami ni nagasare
Arriving at a world familiar yet foreign
tadoritsuita no shitteru you de shiranai sekai deshita
My Big Sister's
Perfect Food!
Null, it's morning.
Time to get up. You'll be late for school.
Snoozing after Sis wakes me...
Shnooshin' affer Shish wakesh 'e...
Snoooozing aaafteeer Siiis waaakes meee...
Snoozing after Sis wakes me...
Good morning, Null!
What the—
How long have I been down here?
Now, eat your breakfast
so you can have a productive day!
Did you make all this, Sis?!
Wowee! It all looks so yummy!
Time to eat...
Huh?
Don't tell me...
I can also adjust the color balance. Voilà!
How is that even useful?
Rich food is bad for you, so you'll
have to make do with just looking at it.
Here, you can eat this.
Oh, almost forgot.
Dark fried rice!
Okay, say "aaaaah!
Peta's "signature dish"...
Um, Sis? Can I give up on this challenge?
But nutrition-wise,
fried rice is the perfect dish.
That's not the point...
Its cost-performance ratio is wonderful, too.
Also not the point.
I know how it looks,
but it's a bamboo shoot—
Not the point!
Null.
Say "aaaaah"!
I don't need it!
No, thank you! Hard pass!
Null.
Wh-What is it, Peta?
Say "aaaaah"!
I knew it...
You're not gonna get me!
You're a slippery one, aren't ya?
But you won't get away!
Say "aaaaah"!
I don't think so!
Did that do it!?
That's one ex-plate of fried rice!
I made her a little too durable!
Sis, forgive me!
CLICK
Peta...
Null!
Peta!
Thank good... ness?
Null!
Sorry for making you wait.
No... No!
You have to open your eyes, sis!
That fried rice would bring
anyone to their knees!
Say "aaaaah"!
I didn't make it to school today, either.