Experiment No. 15
Coitsu Nate Luna D
S-so sleepy...
"Are you all right, Ma'am?"
You should be askin'!
Love always drives me, and yet
The wind against the glass
creates an image of you
What "color" will that wind be today?
I want to experience it, completely
Off in the corners of the classroom
Through the tiniest of magics
Another miracle occurs!
A premonition of love
My heart shouldn't be so uneasy,
I don't know what's next
Aah! What is it that throws
my heart into turmoil?
This sudden spark
Love always drives me, and yet
Someone, someday, deliver
these feelings to you!
LAB
"Were you up late last night?"
You should be askin'!
"So then, that means...?"
I'm not sure what to make
of that last part there...
But, Ma'am, if you're that tired,
shouldn't you just go home?
No!
I don't wanna go home today!
You don't say...
"And why don't you want to go home?"
You should be askin'!
It's as if the words bounce right off you!
You're like the egg crate
soundproofing foam that's on the
walls in the music room!
Ma'am, you don't seem
sleepy at all right now...
Listen up, Tanaka: There are times when,
though sleep beckons,
the only choice is to persevere!
And it is such cases...
that THIS item is of use!
Coitsu Nate Luna D!
It contains the next-generation
ingredient Siestorin,
which dispels fatigue by
providing the equivalent
of 10 hours' worth of uninterrupted sleep.
This, combined with the effects of the
ingredient henjinate, creates a "sub-personality"
that allows for thought processes
distinct from the conscious self.
In other words, these pills allow one to engage
in rational dialogue even when asleep!
Now take one!
Uh, no, I'm not really sleepy.
You should try this one out yourself, Ma'am.
What's this, Tanaka-kun?
Could it be that you haven't noticed?
Today, when I came back to the classroom...
Till just a little while ago,
Yamashita and I were COMPLETELY asleep!
Today, when I came back to the classroom...
YEAH, YEAH.
ASLEEP
As of now, Yamashita
remains in a deep slumber!
Huh? But she's reading a book and...
SUPREME
ENLIGHTENMENT
An Introduction to the Items
of Buddhist Ritual NAMU
Ah! If you look closely,
she's actually sleeping!
Go on, say something to Yamashita's
well-formed sub-personality!
Okay.
Yamashita-san? Are you awake?
Direct all questions to my lawyer.
That's one aggressive personality...
Are you awake, Yamashita-san?
I had a dream I was being sexually harassed.
I'm sorry, Yamashita,
but Tanaka WAS sexually harassing you just now.
Please stop spreading lies.
Main
So, as you can see, conversation is possible
Sub
without a direct link to
the sleeping consciousness.
It seems sort of like sleepwalking.
And now it is YOUR turn, Tanaka.
One can never have too much data!
When you take this, you
will enter a deep sleep.
I have a bad feeling.
Oh, no! I really am getting sleep...
Tanaka, are you asleep?
I am.
Are you REALLY asleep?
I am asleep.
I don't know...
What finger is this?
Your left pinky.
Oh, yeah? And what's your favorite food?
I like the outer skin of daifuku rice cakes.
Which do you prefer, long hair or short?
I like long hair.
Ooh, really?
Ma'am.
O-oh, yeah.
Now then, to get right to the point...
Hey, Tanaka.
The thing is...
Tanaka, would you say your
feelings for me are-?
Ma'am, how did I do?
Staaaare
Ma'am, I'm awake. Like, completely awake.
Ma'am?
I'm so... asleep!
Ma'am? W-wait! Ma'am!
Are you going home already? It's quite early.
Yes, go back, hngrh...
SCIENCE
Please be careful.
I wonder if she'll be all right...
The trial regarding this
sexual harassment case shall now begin!
Please don't be fooled by this.
I sentence the gutter trash
of a defendant named "Tanaka" to death!
Objection.
SCIENCE
Experiment No. 16
Pero-Lilion
You're late, Tanaka!
Is my brother here?
They're not going to know
who "my brother" is.
Oh, yeah.
Is a 2nd-year named "Tanaka" here?!
Watch your tone!
No, Tanaka the 2nd-year hasn't shown up yet.
See? I told you we should
ask the teachers first.
I'M the one who said that.
Ah, Yamashita-san!
You're in the same study club as well?
Is she in your class?
That's right. Wait, don't
you know who that is?
She's Tanaka-sempai's younger sister.
Well, the thing is-
Wait, Yamashita-san!
It would seem some
introductions are in order.
I'm Mizuna Tanaka from
Class 1-2. My favorite food
is the fillings of
traditional Japanese candy.
I'm Yomogi Tanaka from Class 1-6.
My favorite flavor is chocolate mint!
I'm the older twin sister...
And I'm the younger!
Wait, twins?!
Yamashita-san, is this the
first time to hear we're twins?
Well, we're not a lot alike.
Do you mind if we wait here
till our brother shows up?
Feel free.
Strange... How could I
have not known about this?
Still, in the past, I have spotted multiple
Tanaka heads poking out from the crowd.
I thought I was hallucinating,
but looking back, I guess it was these two.
And yet, what does it mean that
Tanaka hasn't mentioned them even once?!
Staaare.
You want one?
Yaay!
This candy is SO delicious!
Me too! I want one!
Wow, you're right! It's choco-mint!
Huh? It tastes like soy flour, right?
What are you talking about, Mizuna-chan?
There's not a trace of soy flour in this!
Yeah, well, I'm not seeing
any signs of choco-mint either!
Sorry I'm late.
Ah! Brother!
Hey, Big Brother, look!
What flavor do you think this candy is?
Personally, I think it
tastes like rice flour.
What are you doing here?
And did you bring that candy to school?
No, your club president gave it to us!
Oh, really? It's all right if they have this?
S-sure, yeah.
It looks like something that she's made...
You two, give that back right now.
Come on, Big Brother, just listen!
This has a robust flavor, but then
the sweetness of the soybeans really packs a punch,
resulting in the ideal flavor profile!
The slight bitterness of
the chocolate enveloped
in sweet mint makes for
a brisk taste sensation!
This is the picture of choco-mint!
What about this is choco-mint?!
Every single one of your taste buds is wrecked!
If THIS tastes like soy flour,
you must think sand tastes pretty sweet!
Brother!
Tell us once and for all what flavor this is!
Hey!
Cut that out.
Come on! Come on!
Stop it!
Don't put things in your mouth and
then try giving them to other people!
SHOCK
It's not like we're strangers...
And don't go splitting hairs!
You need to stop always acting like children.
This is why I don't introduce
you to other people.
You haven't even shown your respects
to the club captain, have you?
Mizuna-chan...
No, we haven't.
Having you two around here
has embarrassed me to no end.
Hey! You'll make Yomogi-chan cry!
I'm the one who wants to cry!
You two, line up.
You're going to apologize to the club captain.
I'm very sorry, Ma'am.
We're sorry.
No, no, really, it's fine.
Look, I have another candy
here. There's one more.
Ma'am, I have a favor I'd like to ask.
Could you please explain
how the candy works to these two?
If you do that, the way you always do,
I think they'll understand
just what they've done.
O-oh, yeah...
Please.
Please!
Still, I mean, you know...
I feel like the weather's turning bad.
I think maybe we should just
call it quits for today.
There, you see?! You're the
ones responsible for this!
You need to own up to what you've done!
Stop casually smacking us on the head!
We're not bongos, you know!
We're members of the Tanaka family,
not percussion instruments!
The Pero-Lilion uses the newly discovered,
next-century sweetener lolilion
to create a candy that has
no direct effect upon the body.
Instead, it induces a hallucinatory sense
of whatever the taster regards as "sweet."