Experiment No. 23
GAN-Q
LAB
Experiment No. 23
GAN-Q
Hey, Ueno!
They all broke at once! These eyeball things.
Love always drives me, and yet…
The wind against the glass
creates an image of you
What "color" will that wind be today?
I want to experience it, completely
Off in the corners of the classroom
Through the tiniest of magics
Another miracle occurs!
A premonition of love
My heart shouldn't be so uneasy,
I don't know what's next
Aah! What is it that throws
my heart into turmoil?
This sudden spark
Love always drives me, and yet…
Someone, someday, deliver
these feelings to you!
Aaand, there.
There's no way all these could break at once!
Lend me your glasses.
What is all this?
Well, lemme tell ya...
Girls kinda don't like being peeped at and stuff,
so when I found this I was like, "BOOM"!
That explanation was nowhere near sufficient!
It would seem that some MALES have come
peeping on the Gymnastics Club during training,
and the girls are none too pleased about it.
So! That is why I made THIS!
The GAN-Q!
Footage from eight separate
eyeball-shaped drones is
simultaneously sent to a
dedicated visor-type monitor,
allowing for independent and
wide-area search of possible hostiles.
The design is such that should a club member
wear these, any peeper would be instantly detected!
I get it. So then, the
Gymnastic Club's, um...
I'm the club captain, Unogawa!
BAM!
Well? Can you fix them?
I AM fixing them. Just wait a minute.
So, how are these, would you say?
Huh?
Like, how do they work.
Well, yeah, I guess they work, but
it's kind of a hassle and stuff
and I get distracted and all that...
How come I gotta be the one on lookout duty?
Because you're the club leader.
Oh, I know! YOU should be on lookout, Ueno.
I have nothing to do with
the Gymnastics Club.
There ya go, like this doesn't concern you...
Hey, why don't you give
gymnastics a shot? C'mon, yeah? C'mon.
Not my problem.
Hey! What's up with this belly?!
Stop that.
It's a bit flabby, wouldn't you say?
You need to exercise more!
Why not try out for
gymnastics, huh? Gymnastics!
Water Storage and Management
for the Aftermath
The legends passed down to us
say that gymnastics is best for this!
Oh, be quiet.
LAB
So, what does this "Science Club" do?
Like, everyone's just on their own.
You're all getting flabby
stomachs because you're so lazy!
And then, there's this ass!
Stop that!
Take a look at this body of mine, yeah?
It's a miracle of this world, perhaps?
You're not all that different
from me, you know.
Nah, don't compare THIS to
that flabby body of yours.
Um... Can I ask something?
Whatcha want?
Are you two...
close like THAT?
What do you mean, "Like THAT"?
Yeah, we're like THAT.
WHAT DO MEAN, "LIKE THAT"?
What do you mean, "Like THAT"?
Um, well, it's hardly my place to say, but...
There's such a thing as politeness,
even between friends,
So talking about physical attributes
is... how can I put this?
They say the skeletal structure
between men and women is different,
so I feel bad for even making a comparison...
You ain't made no comparison.
Um, well, it's about what
you mentioned earlier...
Um, I'm sorry. I think maybe
I'm not using the right words.
Um, the thing is... First of all,
Unogawa-senpai, you're a man, right?
I'M A WOMAN!
Huh?
Why are you so surprised?!
Well, you've been talking
like a man, haven't you?
You got a problem with that?
Your standards of judgment are WAY off!
You can tell by looking, right?!
Ueno! This fool is just rude!
Yeah, he's rude.
Okay, look HERE.
See? Look here. These are what girls wear.
Yes, that's true...
See? Look! Check 'em!
That's not the way to show those!
Thank you, Ueno!
Well, see you!
Hey! You left some of your eyes behind!
SCIENCE
I swear...
Hey, dullard! I don't care
if you didn't mean any harm:
mistaking a girl for a boy is in no way cool.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Unogawa basically says
what she thinks and listens when she wants.
So I don't think she's too beat up about it.
So, you know... I'm not that upset, either.
Understood.
You know, I'm sort of relieved.
Yeah.
...Aren't you going to ask
WHAT he's relieved about?
Tambo! Tam...bo!
Yamashita, what's with you?
LAB
Yo, Tanaka!
Experiment No. 24
Ballet-tan
Yes, what is it?
Death by Tofu
Experiment No. 24
Ballet-tan
Yo, Tanaka!
Yes, what is it?
If this MYSTERIOUS gum is desired by many,
by what means would you procure it?
Well, let's see... We could
break it up to share with-
Shut that mouth!
Material sharing has been
relegated to the past!
Now is the age of exchange
based on EMOTION...
Through the use of the Ballet-tan!
The Ballet-tan!
The encephalic unit measures primary sensory
elements transmitted to the gustatory area,
and then, upon redirecting the
parsed data to the ring-shaped armlet,
shares that information via handshake
to whomever wears the same device,
allowing the recipient to vicariously share
in the taste experience of the primary wearer.
SWEET!!
So, basically, shaking hands will directly
transmit how you think things taste and stuff.
You've pointed a lost alien
family in the right direction.
Collect 10 million yen
and advance 10 spaces.
That seems like it would be really useful.
You've pointed a lost alien
family in the right direction.
Collect 10 million yen
and advance 10 spaces.
*FOR ILLUSTRATIVE PURPOSES
Still, it's not how something actually tastes:
it's your perception of HOW it tastes.
All right, let's try this thing out!
What flavor is this mysterious gum?
Think you can grab a paw and figure it out?!
Oh, sorry. I forgot to put it
on, which is sort of the point.
Right now, we were just holding hands.
Ma'am?
Do you not want to try it out?
Whoa-whoa-whoa, well, yeah!
So, let's get on with it.
Yamashita, you stay on my right.
So, starting out with the gum, we'll...
Y-Yamashita?
Are you ready?
Yes, all ready! Hurry up with that gum!
Okay, here goes.
Oh! Yes, there we go!
This flavor is... Well, Yamashita,
let's say it together.
One, two... Cantalou-
I'm not getting anything.
The flavor hasn't reached me.
I-I wonder why that is...
Because that person there
isn't holding your hand right.
What, so, here?
Yes. There.
Yamashita!
Ma'am, please pull yourself together.
It's all right to just say it.
Say, "Interlock your fingers with mine."
SHOCK!
HNGRARRGH
Um, I'm really sorry, but...
It looks like the signal
just isn't quite enough.
It's the WAY the hands are being held...
The fingers...
The fingers should be reciprocal, as in...
Might as that you please
thrust them into mine?
Oh, okay. Understood.
You mean, how couples hold hands, right?
Um! I'm quite sorry, but...
On my end, it was meant as
something not quite that serious!
It's troubling to have this
thought in such a manner!
SIGH
Actually, come to think of it,
I have some errands to run today.
So, let's call quits here and now! BYE!
B-bye...
Tanaka-senpai.
Huh?
Ow, ow! Whoa, you're REALLY angry today!