Maybe I should've gone to school after all...
My machine sister has some thorns
kikai no ane ni wa toge ga aru
But she's programmed to have a warm heart
demo demo yawarakai kokoro puroguramu
Have you been eating properly?
gohan wo chanto tabetemasu ka
Make sure you go to school,
gakkou ni mo chanto
and make some friends too!
kayotte tomodachi tsukurimashou
Topology, torus, fractal
topology, torus, fractal
You're daydreaming again, I can see the Z's!
mata sou yatte yumemite guuguu
Null&Peta dove into a sea of geometry
Null&Peta kikagaku no umi ni daibu shite
floating
pukapuka
shaking
yurayura
They're floating around
ukandeiru
Null&Peta were washed over with the waves of math formulae
Null&Peta suushiki no nami ni nagasare
Arriving at a world familiar yet foreign
tadoritsuita no shitteru you de shiranai sekai deshita
Uh, what are you doing?
Appearances can help set the right mood.
Okay, have a safe trip!
I said I'm not going, and I mean it!
I can't let my guard down for—
Watch out for traffic!
Just kidding!
Good thing I made some secret modifications.
A bakery!
A cake shop!
And...
Bye-bye!
There's a Tamaya!
Time for some ice cream!
What the...
Big Sister, Do I
Have to Go to Space?
So that's basically how I ended up here.
This might sound obvious,
but there aren't many people up in space.
There's no one to see.
No one to say "hello" to.
No one to say "good morning" to you.
Greetings are awkward for me,
so I don't really mind that.
No big sister to keep bugging
me to go to school, either.
I'm used to being on my own,
but this is enough to make me think
"Wow, I'm really alone."
Null!
You forgot your gym shorts.
What— Sis!?
Want to put them on now?
Ruuuuuuuuumble
Oh, no! Did I not make you
enough fried rice for your lunch?!
Uh, no...
I'll go find something for you to eat!
I found something.
Nutrition-wise, chocolate
is second only to fried rice.
Wh–Where did you even get that?!
Say "Ah!"
I'll die! That would kill me!
Would you prefer this?
Yummy
-----
Miso Ramen
How am I supposed to eat that?!
Like fried rice, ramen is another
nutritionally... perfect... foodstuff...
Peta?
Quit playing around!
Come on, Sis.
Huh?
Don't tell me...
Her battery's dead.
What now?
Maybe I should've gone to school after all...