My machine sister has some thorns
kikai no ane ni wa toge ga aru
But she's programmed to have a warm heart
demo demo yawarakai kokoro puroguramu
Have you been eating properly?
gohan wo chanto tabetemasu ka
Make sure you go to school,
gakkou ni mo chanto
and make some friends too!
kayotte tomodachi tsukurimashou
Topology, torus, fractal
topology, torus, fractal
You're daydreaming again, I can see the Z's!
mata sou yatte yumemite guuguu
Null&Peta dove into a sea of geometry
Null&Peta kikagaku no umi ni daibu shite
floating
pukapuka
shaking
yurayura
They're floating around
ukandeiru
Null&Peta were washed over with the waves of math formulae
Null&Peta suushiki no nami ni nagasare
Arriving at a world familiar yet foreign
tadoritsuita no shitteru you de shiranai sekai deshita
It's weird. The town is back to normal.
I Think Of My Sister,
Therefore My Sister Is
Welcome
Excuse me...
Hello?
I wanted to buy some ice cream.
Sweet Red Bean
Sweet Red Bean Wafer
Oshima
Kombu
Shop
There's no one around.
I'm not sure why,
but I think Peta doesn't want
to talk about what happened.
Whenever I bring it up...
You know how we took on those bugs...
Once the frying pan is on the heat,
leave it for 30 seconds.
Use that time to chop your onions!
...she recites her recipe for fried rice,
after I finally got rid of it all.
Also, the fridge is already full of rice,
as if none of it had been eaten.
Although, it's always like that.
That entire adventure...
Did I dream the whole thing?
But I remember how it felt.
TRY
AGAIN
The heat... the pain...
And I've still got my skinned knee.
We are recruiting!
Speaking of dreams, I've been
having this really weird one lately.
It's a dream about Peta's accident.
I still remember how upset I was.
Pedestrian and
Bicycle Light
This is where...
Where Peta... was hit by a truck.
Pedestrian and
Bicycle Light
It's weird.
Something feels off about this world.
Why am I just noticing
everything that looks out of place?
Was it some unconscious bias that
made me think everything was normal?
A case of apophenia, maybe?
Or maybe it was...
Oh, shoot!
Have I been reincarnated in another world?!
Of course... If this is another world,
this street sign makes perfect sense.
Nooooooo!
Viruses, bugs, corruption...
When my sister passed away,
I made a new one.
I know Peta is real.
The data's all there. I even have
the logs from when I built her.
First chop
the onions,
then
First chop
the onions,
then
First chop
the onions,
then
I'd even say that as long as
Peta's here, this world is real.
I mean, she's my big sister!
Stir-fry your
ingredients
My sister is real.
It was just a coincidence
that downtown was deserted.
And there was no one at school
because it's still summer break.
That's why I know Peta can't be an impostor!
and serve
I think, therefore my sister is.
I think of my sister, therefore I am!
We napped together.
We bathed together.
She read to me.
She carried me.
We even went to space,
and ate snow cones on the beach.
And we saw the savanna together!
This world isn't fake!
I've always been here, and I always will be.
And my big sister will be here with me!
I think, therefore—
Hey, Peta, look! I did it!
Huh? Sis?
Isn't she back yet?
So I guess...
it comes off, huh?