LAB
Experiment No. 13
Panty Roti
We shall now kick off our meeting
Experiment No. 13
Panty Roti
per the Tanaka Panty-Tasting project,
or "TPT" for short.
Tanaka! Panty! Tast-!
Love always drives me, and yet…
The wind against the glass
creates an image of you
What "color" will that wind be today?
I want to experience it, completely
Off in the corners of the classroom
Through the tiniest of magics
Another miracle occurs!
A premonition of love
My heart shouldn't be so uneasy,
I don't know what's next
Aah! What is it that throws
my heart into turmoil?
This sudden spark
Love always drives me, and yet…
Someone, someday, deliver
these feelings to you!
This plan hinges on what can be
divided into three essential elements.
First up is this...
Hunger!
Hunger
Camouflage
Change
This is as it sounds, inciting
Tanaka to feel "hungry."
This has actually already been accomplished.
For the last six months, I
have gradually replaced the
tableware in Tanaka's
home with smaller items.
I have also reduced the amount
of his school lunches by 20%.
GIVE ME THAT!
NO!
As a result, Tanaka is generally gripped
by feelings of hunger,
and in a state of willingness
to eat just about anything.
*"Full"
Now then, does anyone have
any questions so far?
Yes, Yamashita.
Regardless of how hungry Tanaka is,
I don't believe that he would eat panties.
An excellent point, Yamashita.
Indeed, hunger notwithstanding,
he would not eat panties.
The reason for this is...
Panties cannot be eaten!
And yet, Yamashita, what if... What if?!
What if that very premise
could be overcome? What then?!
UENO-SAN'S
SCIENCE COOKING
Ueno-san's Science Cooking!
At first glance, these appear to be cute
yet ordinary panties. Plop!
UENO-SAN'S
SCIENCE COOKING
However, they are composed
of a special fabric made from glutinous rice flour.
By placing them in boiling
water for five minutes,
Boil in Water
the rice flour is simultaneously
broken down and reformed,
becoming a yummy sweet
with a sticky consistency!
All done: the Panty Roti, a newly developed,
hybrid combination of panties
and emergency rations!
This addresses the "Change"
point mentioned prior.
Hm? What is it, Yamashita?
Even if those panties ARE fit for consumption,
I don't believe he would eat them.
Yes! You are correct, Yamashita!
The greatest hurdle to this plan is the
pre-established notion
that panties are NOT for eating.
This the culmination of both knowledge and logic,
which poses quite a problem.
However!
I have already arrived at
the answer to said problem!
Listen up, Yamashita, and look closely.
Just a little bit of massaging, and...
What's this? Could it be
a new form of macaron?!
They're just scrunched-up panties.
Therein lies the final element: camouflage!
That doesn't look camouflaged at all...
Hunger
Hunger!
Change!
Change
Camouflage!
Camouflage
These three elements combine
to form the Trinity Delta Field!
Camouflage
Hunger
Change
Upon noticing that he's sated
his hunger with women's panties,
will Tanaka be able to
keep his wits about him?!
I'm sorry I'm late.
You ARE late, Tanaka, you jackass!
Thanks to you, my body and
spirit AND the object in
question have all completely cooled!
What does that mean?
I got into a fight with the lunch lady
and ended up having a class meeting.
It turns out I actually
WAS being given less food.
Oh. Y-you don't say...
Well, why don't you eat this and rest a bit?
Thanks, I appreciate it.
This guy just ate panties
without even blinking!
He ate it... He ate it!
And with such an unexpected expression!
That was delicious.
I do like those kinds of semi-soft sweets.
O-oh? Hmm...
That really was good.
Do you have any more?
A second serving of panties!
Another one? Well, I'm not sure.
I actually don't recall.
They were a limited release, after all...
No, knowing her, I bet she does.
There'll be the panties she makes him eat,
and another pair she'll
use to prove her point.
I'm guessing... THERE.
Still, going by her reaction,
it seems she didn't expect him to actually eat it.
But, Ma'am! So far everything...
Everything has gone to plan!
The rest is up to how committed you are.
Huh?
Uh, come to think of it...
Yes! That's it, Ma'am!
I think that somewhere around here...
Please show Tanaka-sempai what's what!
There was one more...
Tell him! "What you just
ate... were my panties!"
Too bad, sorry! Looks like I'm all out today.
Oh, jeez.
Lame, lame, lame, lame...
Lame, lame, lame...
AN INTRODUCTION TO
SIDE-TO-SIDE JUMPING
SCIENCE
Experiment No. 14
The Gatcha-Porter
Huh? I'm the first one here today?
Oh. One of those capsule machine things.
Go on and turn it already!
Give it a good turn, and
then remember THAT time!
What time would that be?
You made this, right? If I touch it,
I'm sure you'll just get mad at me.
Hmph! It would seem
you've gotten a sense of it already...
the unequalled DRIVE behind
this future-ish capsule machine!
The Gatcha-Porter!
It deploys a quantum
vacuum force field beyond the device itself,
through which it absorbs
the object in question on a quantum level,
enabling quasi high-speed physical transfer!
When this is activated, it can
instantaneously back-order anything at all!
I don't quite understand how this works.
What exactly gets sent to you?
That is where its true value comes in!
AN ENCYCLOPEDIA OF SOFTENING WATER
Whoever touches the dial on this device
will have his brainwaves scanned,
and anything desired shall
be instantly teleported!
It's like some kind of dream machine!
It IS a dream machine.
Take hold of it, Tanaka!
Try giving it a spin!
Okay!
Before you turn that, visualize
what it is you want.
Victory is mine!
The Gatcha-Porter contains
no brainwave receiver at all!
Instead, the matter that it
teleports has been pre-programmed.
Put simply, what will now appear
has pre-assigned by ME!
Once the dial has been turned,
there can be no going back!
He shall go through life
believing that he is perverted scum
whose desire is that my
garments are easily removed!
MARRIED
Hoping to work together
to build a happy family.
Something came out!
Huh? It looks like a
handkerchief or something.
Open it and see!
Wait, that pattern looks different...
And mine are still on.
No, no! This is all wrong!
I was thinking of something
completely different!
Oh, is that so?
Are you sure that wasn't
what you were thinking of?!
I'm telling you, no, it wasn't!
Ma'am, please, you have to fix this.
Well, I can't see into your head, can I?
Still, this is strange.
Some kind of programming error maybe?
Fine. Try it one more time.
But no excuses: you'll have to
prove what it is you're thinking.
Huh? Is this thing really okay?
Ma'am, some strange black thing came out.
Ma'am! Water came out of
it! Water! What is this?
How should I know?
Just what on Earth are you calling forth?!
Well, I'm going to open it.
SCIENCE
Ah! I knew it would be here!
What the heck? My swimsuit
just suddenly disappeared!
Um, Kitanaga-sempai, this is...
We're testing a machine that will
send you whatever you think of,
but it looks like it's
malfunctioning.  Right, Ma'am?
Fine, just hurry up and give me that back.
I'm sorry.
I swear! You area a pervert... aren't you?
Jeez, Ma'am! Why don't you say anything?!
Now, this another a weird misunderstanding.
Please explain what's going on.
Shut up! Shut your yap and just
do the machine, you legume!
No, I don't want to touch that thing again.
Do it!