LAB
No. 3
THE KILT HIDE
Excuse me! Ueno-san!
No. 3
THE KILT HIDE
About that thing I asked you for...
Ah. Yeah, it's all finished.
Yaay! Thank you!
You can just put it anywhere and that's it.
This really is a big help!
No time like the present...
Kitanaga-san, wait just a minute!
STOP
Huh? What is it?
Well, why are trying to strip?!
I thought I may as well try it out.
Y-you can't do that NOW! I mean,
there's a MAN present!
I don't really mind.
That's not the point.
Maybe the problem is...
this bothers you for a DIFFERENT reason.
Um...
What are you two talking about?
Well, apparently, we've had
someone peeping on our club recently.
I've already informed the teacher,
but because I'm the club captain,
I thought that I should do something too...
That's why she asked me to invent THIS.
The Kilt Hide.
It measures and modulates
the wave nature of light in the surrounding area,
projecting psuedostereoscopic imagery
upon any visual input that
evokes lustful feelings.
Thus, even should one be
ogled by a camera-wielding pervert...
it's capable of blocking
access to all "sexy zones."
STRIP
CUT THAT OUT!
Quit trying to get naked, Kitanaga-san!
Huuh? C'mon...
I have to try it here to see if it works.
Yamashita!
Jeez, Ueno-san!
Look, hurry up and get dressed
while you're in the clear!
The. Whole. Point...
...is that a guy sees,
or it's all for nothing.
Tanaka-kun, was it?
What do you think about THIS?
Uh, well, you're being covered
up by some black things.
Hmm... Maybe my question wasn't quite clear.
Answer again while imagining
the whole scenario.
You're sneaking a peek on
the Swimming Club, when...
you see those young girls
changing into their swimsuits...
their bodies all like THIS.
Does that get you aroused at all?
That's what I'm asking.
M-m-my tit-tit... My titties!
You tried to touch my titties!
Dammit, Tanaka! Damn you!
I'm sorry, but you've got the wrong idea!
I wasn't trying to touch her...
I was just curious what THAT'S all about.
My titties?!
No, not that  those black things.
What are they even attached to?
You idiot! Don't get sidetracked
by something totally unrelated!
It's kind of a three-dimensional
image projected into the air, okay?!
Can you move it around?
CUT IT OUT!
Hey. Over here.
Y-Yamashita!
What is that?!
Yes! Tanaka's gotten distracted.
Put this on while you got the chance! Put it on!
I was a little worried when
I heard how much she's been stressing about this...
Look, look... Looky, looky, looky...
Hey, come on! What is that?
but it looks like they're
actually having fun.
Well, I should be heading back now.
Oh, you're leaving?
I'm glad I got to see a different
side of you, Ueno-san.
I'll be back sometime soon to hang out again.
Hey! You forgot all this!
Kitanaga-saaan!
Experiment No. 6
Garakutan
Aah, I'm so thirsty. Aaaah!
You want some barley tea?
AAAH, WHATEVER SHALL I DO?!
Oh, that's right!
I brought THIS today!
That was some bad acting.
So, what is that?
Garakutan!
By rotating clockwise with just the right amount of force
it's able to reach out to our galaxy,
MILKY WAY-SAN!
and in mere moments produce
fresh-tasting water.
MILKY WAY-SAN!
By: Milky Way
LEAVE IT TO ME!
Act now to receive this special
three-vial set! BA-BAAM!
SUITABLE FOR FAMILY & FRIENDS!
All right, pay attention,
dammit. Turn the lid like this, and...
So, where did the water come from?
You just tune people out, don't you, Tanaka?!
This water...
came from the Milky Way!
That doesn't make sense.
And now, young man,
I give you the water of the Milky Way itself!
Thanks.
Go on! Gulp it down!
Huh? No, I'm fine. YOU'RE the
one who's thirsty, right?
Actually, is this water even
safe to drink? It's kind of suspicious...
Hey! That's an insult to our galaxy!
Give me that!
I swear...
Aah, the flavor of the Milky Way!
That's way too enigmatic.
Well?! Do you get it now?
Okay, it's your turn to drink.
I'm really not very thirsty.
Just shut up and drink already!
You sure are pushy...
Aah, the flavor of the Milky Way!
GRAAAARGH!
Why did you have to an open up a new one?!
Sorry.
This one's already open!
Well, I mean...
You put your lips on that one, right?
SHOCK!
I've never been a fan of
sharing the same drink with someone.
It's just... off-putting.
I'm sure you like it even
less than me, right?
Huh?
I mean, a BOY is putting his
mouth where yours has been.
That sort of thing bothers
girls even more, right?
Gah! I-I don't worry about
i-i-indirect kisses or things of that nature, actually!
Ah, I swear! You boys,
you scary boys think about that every single day!
It's all part of puberty, yes!
So our lips happen to touch the same spot, so what?!
What meaning would such an action even have?!
You're overthinking things,
yes, very strange things!
Ma'am. I get it. Go on,
place your lips where mine have been.
It should be no big deal, right?
HUH?! Well, of course not!
You rubbed your tongue all
over this thing, didn't you?
Yes, you really tongued this thing.
L... Lick, lick... Lick, lick...
Lick... Lick?
LAB
Oh, no. Are you okay?
See? You DON'T want to
put mouth there, right?
You don't have to force yourself.
I was being a little mean just now.
I'll go get a rag.
Blgh!
Ma'am, that's the one that fell, right?
THIS one's yours.
Ah, yes, that's right! How clumsy of me!
They look so similar! You
can't blame me right?!
Oh my, oh my!